ACTWU's Research Department Company Records 5619/012
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Brite White Laundry Corp. (Flushing, NY), 1964 (Box 22, Folder 71)
- British Van Heusen Shirts (Japanese License), 1971 (Box 22, Folder 72)
- Brittany Ltd. (Chicago, IL), 1975 (Box 22, Folder 73)
- Broadloom Manufacturing Co. (Hartsville, TN), 1974 (Box 22, Folder 74)
- Broadstreet (NYC), 1965-1972 (Box 22, Folder 75)
- Broadway - Hale Stores Inc. (Los Angeles, CA), 1967-1974 (Box 22, Folder 76)
- Broadway Neckwear, Inc. (NYC), 1971 (Box 22, Folder 77)
- Broderick Manufacturing Co. (Parsons, KS), 1973 (Box 22, Folder 78)
- Brody Clothing Co. (Boston, MA), 1966 (Box 22, Folder 79)
- F. Brody & Sons Co. (Des Moines, IA), 1962 (Box 22, Folder 80)
- Bronco Manufacturing Corp. (NYC), 1961 (Box 22, Folder 81)
- Bronx Dyeing & Finishing (Bronx, NY), 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 82)
- Bronzetti-Siegel Co. (Lawrence, MA), 1966 (Box 22, Folder 83)
- Bronzini Neckwear (Division Pacesetter Industries, NYC), 1974-1976 (Box 22, Folder 84)
- Bronzini Shirtmakers (NYC, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 85)
- Brooklyn Quilting Corp. (Brooklyn, NY), 1971-1973 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Brooklyn Yarn Dye Co. (Brooklyn, NY)(Arbitration), 1941 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Brookdale Clothes, Inc. (NYC), 1971-1973 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Brookevale Manufacturing Co. (Monesson, PA), 1968-1976 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Brookfield & Moyer (NYC), 1969 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Brookfield Industries, Inc. (L.I.C., NY), 1962-1974 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Brookport Fashions, Inc. (NYC), 1967 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Brooks, Bobbie, Inc. (Cleveland, OH), 1967-1975 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Brooks, Norman L. & Co. (NYC), 1973 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Brooks Industries Inc. (NYC), 1972-1975 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Brooks Pants (Scranton, PA), 1965 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Brooks Paper Co. (Ordill, IL), 1971 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Brooks Uniform Co. (Division of Blue Bell, Inc., Greensboro, NC), 1968-1972 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Brookshire Sportswear, Inc. (NYC), 1967 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Brookside Industries, Inc. (Reidsville, NC), 1961-1963 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Brookstreet, England, Ltd. (NYC), 1968 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Brookville Glove Manufacturing Co. (Brookville, PA), 1966 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Brothers' Stores Corp. (NYC), 1975 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Brown-Century Corp. (Arbitration), 1951 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Brown-Century Corp. (Lake Village, AR), 1961-1964 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Brown-Dunkin Downtown (Little Rock, AR), 1968 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Brown-Dunkin Northland (Little Rock, AR), 1968 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Brown-Dunkin Southland (Little Rock, AR), 1968 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Brownie's Men's Shop (NYC), 1965 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Browning Arms Co. (Morgantown, UT), 1969 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Browning 5th Ave. (NYC), 1966-1974 (Box 23, Folder 26)
- Browning-King (Milwaukee, WI), 1965 (Box 23, Folder 27)
- Brownwood Manufacturing Co. (Wash., DC), 1964-1967 (Box 23, Folder 28)
- Bruce Products (Downers Grove, IL), 1969 (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Bruce Products, Inc. (Eatontown, NJ), 1963 (Box 23, Folder 30)
- Bruck Mills, Ltd. (Melbourne, Aus.), 1968 (Box 23, Folder 31)
- Brucks, Inc. (St. Louis, MO), 1972 (Box 23, Folder 32)
- Bruder Neckwear Co. (NYC), 1967-1971 (Box 23, Folder 33)
- George Brunssen Inc. (NYC), 1965 (Box 23, Folder 34)
- Brundidge Shirt Co. (Subsidiary Union Underwear Co.), 1969 (Box 23, Folder 35)
- Bru-Sand, Inc. (Miami FL), 1970-1973 (Box 23, Folder 36)
- Brunt-Tanatex, Inc. (Sybron Corp., Calhoun, GA), 1972 (Box 23, Folder 37)
- Lane Bryant (NYC), 1967-1968 (Box 23, Folder 38)
- Buccaneer Slacks (Monroe, LA), 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 39)
- Buck Creek Cotton Mills, Inc. (Columbiana, AL), 1972 (Box 23, Folder 40)
- Buckeye Bobbin & Manufacturing Co. (Westlake, OH), 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 41)
- Buckeye Industries, Inc. (Wrightsville, GA), 1962 (Box 23, Folder 42)
- Buckley & Mann (Franklin, MA), 1974 (Box 23, Folder 43)
- Buddy Togs Inc. (Brooklyn, NY), 1965 (Box 23, Folder 44)
- Budget Uniform Center (Los Angeles, CA), 1968 (Box 23, Folder 45)
- Budget Uniform Shop (Los Angeles, CA), 1968 (Box 23, Folder 46)
- Buffalo Cloth Weaving Co. (Buffalo, NY), 1970 (Box 23, Folder 47)
- Buffalo Dye Works of Allied Chemical Corp. (Buffalo, NY), 1970 (Box 23, Folder 48)
- Buffalo Knitting Mills (NYC), 1969 (Box 23, Folder 49)
- Buffums' (Long Beach, CA), 1968 (Box 23, Folder 50)
- Bulk Yarns, Inc. (Bessemer City, NC), 1971 (Box 23, Folder 51)
- Bullock Hosiery, Inc. (Thomasville, NC), 1968 (Box 23, Folder 52)
- Bundy Corp. (Detroit, MI), 1967 (Box 23, Folder 53)
- Paul Bunyon Outerwear (Wisconsin Rapids, WI), 1962 (Box 23, Folder 54)
- Burberrys (US Distributor in NYC)(Offices London, UK), 1967-1975 (Box 23, Folder 55)
- Burbro Inc. (Los Angeles, CA), 1971 (Box 23, Folder 56)
- Burbrooke Manufacturing Co. (NYC), 1965 (Box 23, Folder 57)
- Burean-Holloway Knitting Mills, Inc. (Jackson Center, OH), 1967 (Box 23, Folder 58)
- Burford Textiles Ltd. (Burford, Ontario), 1972 (Box 23, Folder 59)
- Burdett Apparel Corp. (Heber City, UT), 1968 (Box 23, Folder 60)
- Burgand Shirt (NYC), 1969 (Box 23, Folder 61)
- Burgess Manufacturing Inc. (Cartersville, GA), 1968-1970 (Box 23, Folder 62)
- Burkay Knitting Mills, Inc. (Hamburg, PA), 1968-1969 (Box 23, Folder 63)
- Burkhardt Bros. Co. (Cincinnati, OH), 1969 (Box 23, Folder 64)
- Burlington Fabric Mills (Burlington, NJ), 1937-1958 (Box 23, Folder 65)
- Burlington Mills (Burlington, WI), 1967 (Box 23, Folder 66)
- Bur-Mac Corporation (Athens, GA), 1960-1967 (Box 23, Folder 67)
- Burnham & Co. (Investments - NYC), 1968 (Box 23, Folder 68)
- Frederick H. Burnham Co., Inc. (Michigan City, IN), 1967 (Box 23, Folder 69)
- Burnley Shirt Corp. (NYC), 1960 (Box 23, Folder 70)
- Mel Burns Clothes for Men Inc. (Richmond, VA), 1971 (Box 23, Folder 71)
- Burro Manufacturing Co. (El Paso, TX), 1967-1970 (Box 23, Folder 72)
- Montague Burton, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 73)
- Burton Manufacturing Co., Inc. (NYC), 1958-1963 (Box 23, Folder 74)
- Burton's Stores (NYC), 1969 (Box 23, Folder 75)
- Bussman Manufacturing Division (St. Louis, MO), 1975 (Box 23, Folder 76)
- Butch Sporting Goods, Inc. (Cincinnati, OH), 1971 (Box 23, Folder 77)
- Butler Shirt Co. (Butler, PA), 1961 (Box 23, Folder 78)
- The Butwin Sportswear Co. (St. Paul, MN), 1960-1968 (Box 23, Folder 79)
- Byford Imports, Inc. (D. Byford & Co., Ltd., Barrow-On-Soar, UK), 1967-1974 (Box 23, Folder 80)
- Byrd Industries of Virginia, Inc., 1969-1974 (Box 23, Folder 81)
- C&A Apparel Corp. (Rosebank, NY), 1966-1967 (Box 23, Folder 82)
- C&A Industries (Collins & Aikman Corp., NYC), 1975 (Box 23, Folder 83)
- C&C Clothing Co. Inc. (Philadelphia, PA), 1963 (Box 23, Folder 84)
- C&C Elite Linen Service, Inc. (Washington DC), 1965 (Box 23, Folder 85)
- C & D Sportswear Corp. (Adel, GA), 1958-1962 (Box 23, Folder 86)
- C'Espino Neckwear (Los Angeles, CA), 1973 (Box 23, Folder 87)
- C & F Men's & Boys' Wear Corp. (NYC), 1974 (Box 23, Folder 88)
- C & M Sportswear Manufacturing Co. Inc. (Meshoppen, PA), 1969 (Box 23, Folder 89)
- C & P Inc. (Scranton, PA), 1963 (Box 23, Folder 90)
- C & R Clothiers, Inc. (Los Angeles, CA), 1973-1975 (Box 23, Folder 91)
- C & R Manufacturing Co. (Rector, AR), 1966 (Box 23, Folder 92)
- CBF Garment Co., Inc. (Clinton, NC), 1962 (Box 23, Folder 93)
- C.I.T. Fin. Corp. (NYC), 1960-1968 (Box 23, Folder 94)
- C.M.E. Inc. (Amery, WI), 1976 (Box 23, Folder 95)
- C-R Clothing Co. (Philadelphia, PA), 1967 (Box 23, Folder 96)
- CSM Corp. (W. Swanzey, NH), 1971 (Box 23, Folder 97)
- Cable Car Clothiers (San Francisco, CA), 1969 (Box 23, Folder 98)
- Cable Hampton (Boston, MA), 1972 (Box 23, Folder 99)
- Cable Industries, Inc. (NYC), 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 100)
- Cable Raincoat Co., Inc. (Boston, MA), 1962-1972 (Box 23, Folder 101)
- Cable Ties Manufacturing (Panduit Corp., Tinley Park, IL), 1973 (Box 23, Folder 102)
- Cadillac Clothes, Inc. (Paterson, NJ), 1966-1967 (Box 23, Folder 103)
- Cadillac Overall Supply Co. (Cadillac MI), 1958-1968 (Box 23, Folder 104)
- Cadillac Plastic & Chemical Co. (Detroit, MI), 1973 (Box 23, Folder 105)
- Cadillac Warping & Sizing Co. (Hawthorne, NJ), 1972 (Box 23, Folder 106)
- Cagner, Nat, Inc. (NYC), 1963-1975 (Box 23, Folder 107)
- Calcagni Piece Dye Works Co., Inc. (Bronx, NY), 1973 (Box 23, Folder 108)
- Caldor, Inc. (Norwalk, CT), 1965-1970 (Box 23, Folder 109)
- Caledonia Manufacturing Co. (Caledonia, Miss.), 1975 (Box 23, Folder 110)
- Calhoun Garment Co. (Division Kellwood Co., Oxford, Miss.), 1965 (Box 23, Folder 111)
- Calhoun Manufacturing Co. (Calhoun, GA), 1964 (Box 23, Folder 112)
- California Clothing (Chula Vista, CA), 1968 (Box 23, Folder 113)
- California Cotton Mills (Uniontown, Alabama), 1949-1950 (Box 23, Folder 114)
- California Dyeing & Finishing Co. (Los Angeles, CA), 1973 (Box 23, Folder 115)
- California Girlswear Inc. (Coolidge, AZ), 1966-1968 (Box 23, Folder 116)
- California Hand Prints, Inc. (Hermosa Beach, CA), 1970-1972 (Box 23, Folder 117)
- California Knitwear Co. (Los Angeles, CA), 1967-1972 (Box 23, Folder 118)
- California Life Insurance Co. (Oakland, CA), 1968 (Box 23, Folder 119)
- California Men's & Boys' Apparel Club, Inc. (San Francisco, CA), 1968 (Box 23, Folder 120)
- California Men's Stylist, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 121)
- California Piece Dye Works (Los Angeles, CA), 1974 (Box 23, Folder 122)
- California Sportswear Co. (Chicago, IL), 1973-1975 (Box 23, Folder 123)
- California Swimwear Co. Inc. (Los Angeles, CA), 1972 (Box 23, Folder 124)
- California Weavers, Inc. (Los Angeles, CA), 1970 (Box 23, Folder 125)
- Caligen Foam Ltd. (Accrington, Lancashire, UK), 1964 (Box 23, Folder 126)
- Calina Industries, Inc. (Marion, SC), 1971-1973 (Box 23, Folder 127)
- Caliper Tailors, Ltd. (Division Aberle Industries Inc., Philadelphia, PA), 1969 (Box 23, Folder 128)
- Cal-Made Manufacturing Co. (Los Angeles, CA), 1962 (Box 23, Folder 129)
- Calloway Shirt Co. Inc. (Murray, KY), 1962-1976 (Box 23, Folder 130)
- Calsun Co. (Los Angeles, CA), 1964-1968 (Box 23, Folder 131)
- Caltesco Midwest, Inc. (Carbondale, IL), 1969-1970 (Box 23, Folder 132)
- Cal-Ute Corporation (Fillmore, UT), 1968-1969 (Box 23, Folder 133)
- Calvert Clothes (Baltimore, MD), 1957-1962 (Box 23, Folder 134)
- Cambelford Cloth Co. (Cambelford, Ont.), 1972 (Box 23, Folder 135)
- Cambridge Clothes (Hamilton, Ont.), 1968 (Box 23, Folder 136)
- Cambridge Tailoring Co. (Baltimore, MD), 1970 (Box 23, Folder 137)
- Camden Felling Shop (Camden, NJ), 1966 (Box 23, Folder 138)
- Camden Yarns Inc. (Lisbon Falls, ME), 1973 (Box 23, Folder 139)
- Camelot Garment, Inc. (Stapleton, NY), 1968 (Box 23, Folder 140)
- Cameo Binding Co. (NYC), 1974 (Box 23, Folder 141)
- Camouflage Manufacturing Co. (Jacksonville, FL), 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 142)
- S.H. Camp & Co. (Warrior, Alabama), 1964 (Box 23, Folder 143)
- Camp Industries (Reading, PA), 1973 (Box 23, Folder 144)
- Camp Industries, Inc. (Nashville, TN), 1975 (Box 23, Folder 145)
- Camp & McInnes, Inc. (NYC), 1968-1971 (Box 23, Folder 146)
- Phil Campbell Manufacturing Co. (Birmingham, AL), 1965-1968 (Box 23, Folder 147)
- Campbellford Cloth Co. Ltd. (Campbellford, Ontario, Canada), 1970-1975 (Box 23, Folder 148)
- Camping Equipment (Division of Colorado Sports Industries, Denver, CO), 1969 (Box 23, Folder 149)
- Camptown Togs, Inc. (Clanton, AL), 1963 (Box 23, Folder 150)
- Campus Casuals of CA, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 151)
- Canadian Clothiers Corp. (Toronto, Canada), 1966-1971 (Box 23, Folder 152)
- Canadian Gypsum Co., Ltd. (Weston, Ontario, Canada), 1972 (Box 23, Folder 153)
- Canadian U.S. Knitting, Ltd. (St. Hyacinthe, Que.), 1972 (Box 23, Folder 154)
- Canadians Industries, Ltd. (Montreal, Canada), 1971 (Box 23, Folder 155)
- CANNON MILLS Co. (see Reference Sheet for folder identification). 1974 Campaign #1 - General (Box 24, Folder 1)
- CANNON MILLS Co. (see Reference Sheet for folder identification). 1974 Campaign #2 - Leaflets (Box 24, Folder 2)
- CANNON MILLS Co. (see Reference Sheet for folder identification). 1976 Campaign - Leaflets (Box 24, Folder 3)
- CANNON MILLS Co. (see Reference Sheet for folder identification). Annual Reports, 1951-1976 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- CANNON MILLS Co. (see Reference Sheet for folder identification). Financial #1 1935-1957 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- CANNON MILLS Co. (see Reference Sheet for folder identification). Financial #2 1958-1976 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- CANNON MILLS Co. (see Reference Sheet for folder identification). General Labor 1939-1976 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Cannon Tailoring Co. (Cleveland, OH), 1959-1974 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Canoe Underwear Co. (Pine Grove, PA), 1974 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Canteen Corp. (Canteen Food & Vending Services Division, Painesville, OH), 1972 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Canteen Corp. (Chicago, IL), 1968 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Canterbury Belts, Inc. (NYC), 1967-1969 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Canterbury Shop (Dallas, TX), 1967 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Canvas Products Co. (St. Louis, MO), 1968 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Canvil, Ltd. (Simcoe, Ont.), 1975 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Cap-Roc, Inc. (Rochester, NY), 1964-1969 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Capco Sales Corp. (NYC), 1965 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Cape Cod Sportswear (New Bedford, MA), 1966-1970 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Capel Coat Corp. (NYC), 1969 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Capici Coat Shop, Inc. (Philadelphia, PA), 1964-1966 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Capital City Woolen Mills, Inc. (Des Moines, IA), 1971 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Capital District Dy-Dee Service, Inc. (Schenectady, NY), 1960-1964 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Capital Knitting Mills, Inc. (NYC), 1973 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Capital Laundry & Dry Cleaning Co., Inc. (Louisville, KY), 1964-1965 (Box 24, Folder 24)
- Capital Plastics, Inc. (Rochester, NY), 1968 (Box 24, Folder 25)
- Capital Shirt Corp. (NYC), 1960-1961 (Box 24, Folder 26)
- Capitol Bias Products, Inc. (NYC), 1972 (Box 24, Folder 27)
- Capitol Glove-Hyman Krasna, Inc. (NYC), 1967 (Box 24, Folder 28)
- Capitol Knitting Mills, Inc. (Little Falls, NJ), 1971-1973 (Box 24, Folder 29)
- Caporale Brothers Engraving (Hackensack, NJ), 1976 (Box 24, Folder 30)
- Capper & Capper (Chicago, IL & Troy, MI), 1968-1969 (Box 24, Folder 31)
- J. Capps & Sons Ltd. (Chicago, IL), 1960-1974 (Box 24, Folder 32)
- Caprito Pants, Inc. (NYC), 1968 (Box 24, Folder 33)
- Caradco, Inc. (Dubuque, IA), 1968 (Box 24, Folder 34)
- Caravelle Wood Products, Inc. (Chicago Heights, IL), 1970-1975 (Box 24, Folder 35)
- Carbery, Wm. J. (NYC), 1975 (Box 24, Folder 36)
- Carbon Hill Manufacturing Co. Inc. (Carbon Hill, AL), 1962-1963 (Box 24, Folder 37)
- Carbon Textile Processing Co. (Port Carbon, PA), 1972 (Box 24, Folder 38)
- Carborundum Co. (Niagara Falls, NY), 1969-1975 (Box 24, Folder 39)
- Cardale Manufacturing Co., Inc. (NYC), 1967 (Box 24, Folder 40)
- Cardinal Clothes (NYC), 1967 (Box 24, Folder 41)
- Cardinal Knitting Mills, Inc. (Philadelphia, PA), 1963 (Box 24, Folder 42)
- Cardinal Manufacturing Co., Inc. (Etowah, TN), 1960 (Box 24, Folder 43)
- Care Leather (Gloversville, NY), 1969 (Box 24, Folder 44)
- Career Apparel, Inc. (Chicago, IL), 1972-1974 (Box 24, Folder 45)
- Career Clothes, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 46)
- Career Girl Manufacturing Co. (Dallas, TX), 1971 (Box 24, Folder 47)
- Career Wear (Cleveland, OH), 1968 (Box 24, Folder 48)
- Carefree Casuals, Inc. (NYC), 1969 (Box 24, Folder 49)
- Caressa, Inc. (Miami, FL), 1964 (Box 24, Folder 50)
- Carey Clothing Co. (Baltimore, MD), 1962-1970 (Box 24, Folder 51)
- Carey-McFall Co. (Montoursville & Williamsport, PA), 1972-1974 (Box 24, Folder 52)
- Philip Carey Manufacturing Co. (Cincinnati, OH), 1967-1969 (Box 24, Folder 53)
- Caribe Gloves, Inc. (Jamestown, NY), 1966 (Box 24, Folder 54)
- Carlich Mt. Kelly Spring (Milleriken, PA), 1965 (Box 24, Folder 55)
- Carlton, Inc. (Cherryville, NC), 1970-1975 (Box 24, Folder 56)
- Carlton Mills Co., Inc. (Philadelphia, PA), 1970-1975 (Box 24, Folder 57)
- Carlton Sportswear Co. (Winston-Salem, NC), 1968 (Box 24, Folder 58)
- Carlyle Shirt Co., Inc. (NYC -now Subsidiary of Interco), 1966-1976 (Box 24, Folder 59)
- Carmel Weaving (Jersey City, NJ), 1976 (Box 24, Folder 60)
- Carmela Glove, Inc. (Amsterdam, NY), 1965 (Box 24, Folder 61)
- Carnaby, Inc. (Hialeah, FL), 1971 (Box 24, Folder 62)
- Carnac, Inc. (Danville, VA), 1968 (Box 24, Folder 63)
- Carnegie Shirt Corp. (NYC), 1961-1962 (Box 24, Folder 64)
- Carolina American Textiles, Inc. (Greensboro, NO, 1972-1975 (Box 24, Folder 65)
- Carolina Blouse Co. (Greenville, SC), 1974 (Box 24, Folder 66)
- Carolina Carton Co. Inc. (Greenville, SC), 1970 (Box 24, Folder 67)
- Carolina Fiberglass Products, Inc. (Wilson, NC), 1972 (Box 24, Folder 68)
- Carolina Sportswear Co. (Warrenton, NC), 1960-1961 (Box 24, Folder 69)
- Carolina Underwear Co., Inc. (Thomasville, NO, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 70)
- Carolyn Chenilles of Canada, Ltd. (Acton Vale, Que., Can.), 1974 (Box 24, Folder 71)
- Carroll Knits, Inc. (Eden, NC), 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 72)
- Johnny Carson Apparel, Inc. (Atlanta, GA), 1969-1975 (Box 24, Folder 73)
- Carter & Churchill Co., 1960-1967 (Box 24, Folder 74)
- Carter & Holmes, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 75)
- Carter Bros./Chattanooga, Tenn., 1971 (Box 24, Folder 76)
- Carter-Day Textile Operation (Carter-Day)/Minneapolis, MN, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 77)
- Carter, H.W. & Sons, Inc. (Cross Reference to Ringer Co.), 1968-1975 (Box 24, Folder 78)
- Carter Industries, Inc./Olive Hill, Ky., 1964 (Box 24, Folder 79)
- Carter Industrial Laundry, Inc., 1964 (Box 24, Folder 80)
- Carter, J. W. & Co. (Nashville, TN), 1967 (Box 24, Folder 81)
- Carters Discount Stores Inc., 1969 (Box 24, Folder 82)
- Carter's Ink Co./Grossville, Tenn., 1974 (Box 24, Folder 83)
- Carteret Industries/Newport, NC, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 84)
- Carthage Garment Corp./Carthage, Mississippi, 1964-1965 (Box 24, Folder 85)
- Carthage Mills/Cincinnati, OH, 1970-1976 (Box 24, Folder 86)
- Casa Dei Bronzetti, 1966-1967 (Box 24, Folder 87)
- Casa Grande Mills (Division Parsons & Baker Co.), 1963-1971 (Box 24, Folder 88)
- Case Fashions, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 89)
- Casemakers, Inc., 1972 (Box 24, Folder 90)
- Casey's Sporting Goods, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 91)
- Cashmere Imports, Ltd., 1964-1965 (Box 24, Folder 92)
- Cashmere Processing Corp., 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 93)
- Cashnyl Knit Goods Processing Co., 1971 (Box 24, Folder 94)
- Casselberry Manufacturing Co., 1967 (Box 24, Folder 95)
- Cast Optics, 1968-1970 (Box 24, Folder 96)
- Castaways, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 97)
- Castle Creek Prints, Inc., 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 98)
- Castle Enterprises, Inc., 1969 (Box 24, Folder 99)
- Castlerock Knitwear, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 100)
- Castleton Industries, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 101)
- Casual Sportswear Company, Inc., 1961-1968 (Box 24, Folder 102)
- Casual Wear (Division of Arrow Co.), 1973 (Box 24, Folder 103)
- Casualcraft, Inc., 1965-1975 (Box 24, Folder 104)
- Casualcraft, Inc. (Mohawks Sportswear), 1975 (Box 24, Folder 105)
- Catalina, Inc., 1960-1978 (Box 24, Folder 106)
- Catalina of California, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 107)
- Catalog Chain, 1972-1976 (Box 24, Folder 108)
- Catalog Fashions, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 109)
- Catania Clothes of Fifth Avenue, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 110)
- Catawba Yarns, Inc., 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 111)
- Cavalier Bag Company, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 112)
- Cavalier Imports, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 113)
- Cavanaugh Brand, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 114)
- Burlington Industries, Inc. Financial. ANNUAL REPORTS - (1951-1976), 1951-1978 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Burlington Industries, Inc. FINANCIAL #IV (1960-1975), 1955-1975 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Burlington Industries, Inc. FINANCIAL #III (1956-1959), 1950-1965 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Burlington Industries, Inc. FINANCIAL #II (1948-1955) (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Burlington Industries, Inc. FINANCIAL #I (1937-1947) (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Burlington Industries, Inc. FINANCIAL & GENERAL I (1956-1976) (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Financial. GENERAL LABOR II (1955-1976), 1955-1957 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Financial. GENERAL LABOR I (1937-1955) (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Financial. (TWUA Report on Mills Closed 1940-1961), 1938-1961 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Financial. (TWUA Southern Campaign Bulletins, 1955) (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Financial. GENERAL LABOR II/ERWIN MILLS Division (1950-1976) (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Financial. FINANCIAL III/ERWIN MILLS Division (1950-1975) (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Financial. ERWIN MILLS, ERWIN, NC/Folder #1 (1944-45), 1937-1945 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Financial. ERWIN MILLS, ERWIN, NC/Folder #2 (1945-1975) (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Financial. ERWIN MILLS #1, 4 & 6/DURHAM, NC/Folder #1, 1937-1943 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Financial. ERWIN MILLS 1, 4 & 6/DURHAM, NC/Folder #2, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Financial. ERWIN MILLS #1, 4 & 6/DURHAM, NC/Folder #3, 1941-1951 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Financial. ERWIN MILLS #1, 4 & 6/DURHAM, NC/Folder #4, 1942-1986 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Financial. BURLINGTON INDUSTRIES (Note: Entire Box 6 is Burlington Industries), 1976 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Financial. ERWIN MILLS #3, COOLEMEE, NC Folder #1 (Arbitrations), 1941-1951 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Financial. ERWIN MILLS #3, COOLEMEE, NC Folder #2 (Plant Analysis), 1949 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Financial. ERWIN MILLS #3, COOLEMEE, NC Folder #3 (Weavers Analysis), 1942-1949 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Financial. ERWIN MILLS #3, COOLEMEE, NC Folder #4 (Arbitration Association), 1950-1952 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Financial. ERWIN MILLS #3, COOLEMEE, NC Folder #5 (Weavers/Fixers), 1950 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Financial. ERWIN MILLS #3, COOLEMEE, NC Folder #6 (Wages/Conditions), 1938-1950 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Financial. ERWIN MILLS #3, COOLEMEE, NC Folder #7 (1944-1947) (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Financial. ERWIN MILLS #3, COOLEMEE, NC Folder #8 (1945-1947 Arbitration) (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Financial. ERWIN MILLS #7, DIANA COTTON, NEUSE, NC (1947-'59), 1948-1959 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Financial. HESS GOLDSMITH Division/FINANCIAL (1937-1966) (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Financial. HESS GOLDSMITH Division/LABOR (1937-1961) (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Financial. HESS GOLDSMITH Division (Atwater Division Arbitrations, 1953 & 1955) (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Financial. KLOPMAN MILLS Division FINANCIAL & GENERAL (1958-1974) (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Financial. MARTEL MILLS Division/FINANCIAL & GENERAL (1940-1958) (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Financial. MARTEL MILLS/LEXINGTON, SC (1940-43), 1943 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Financial. MARTEL MILLS/RED BANK, SC, 1939 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Financial. MARTEL MILLS/VALLEY FALLS MILL, SPARTANBURG, SC, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Financial. (PACIFIC MILLS) FINANCIAL & GENERAL #2 (1956-1959) (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Financial. PACIFIC MILLS/RHODISS, NC, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Financial. (Formerly Lee & Sons Co./Bridgeport, Pa.) FINANCIAL (1937-'62), 1962 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Financial. BURLINGTON MILLS, ALTAVISTA, VA., 1957 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Financial. BURLINGTON HOSIERY Co., ASHEBORO, NC, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Financial. BURLINGTON MILLS, ASHEBORO, NC (Cetwick Plant, Klopman Mills), 1979 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Financial. Catlin Farish Division, Batesburg, SC, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Financial. Burl-Craft Division/Burlington, NC, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Financial. BURLINGTON DECORATIVE FABRICS Association, BURLINGTON, NC, 1957 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Financial. BURLINGTON HOSIERY COMPANY - DOTHAN, ALABAMA, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- Financial. BURLINGTON MILLS - DUBLIN, VIRGINIA (OWNED BY BURLINGTON INDUSTRIES), 1957 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Financial. BURLINGTON MILLS - FAYETTEVILLE, NC (OWNED BY BURLINGTON INDUSTRIES), 1949 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Financial. BURLINGTON HOSIERY Co./FRANKLIN, NC (OWNED BY BURLINGTON INDUSTRIES), 1971 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Financial. BURLINGTON MILLS - FRANKLINTON, NC (OWNED BY BURLINGTON INDUSTRIES), 1952 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Financial. BURLINGTON INTERNATIONAL - GALT, CANADA (OWNED BY BURLINGTON INDUSTRIES), 1957 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- Financial. BURLINGTON MILLS - GASTONIA, NC (FLINT PLANT & RANLO PLANT), 1974 (Box 28, Folder 22)